trendtalky.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy - Trend Talky

We commit to provide our users a safe and secure platform and guarantee their privacy and the data they share with the website. Whether you are our registered user or you are simply visiting our website, your privacy is important to us. We recommend you to read our statement of privacy policy to comprehend what sort of personal data we obtain from users and how we utilize it.

We encourage you to share your details and get registered with us in order to provide you best quality services. In order to become our registered member, you shall provide us your name, email address, username, password and password validation. When you visit and navigate on our website, some of our services may direct you to third party web domains. Personal information shared by you with these third parties web domains will be dealt according to their privacy policy. Our website shall not be responsible for the information you share with these third party web domains. This privacy policy only deals with the personal information you share with us and we are not liable to protect your information provided to these third party domains. We also recommend you to be careful while sharing your personal details with third party domains. We do not guarantee, support and admit the product or information accessible at these third parties web domains, nor does a link show any connection or relation by the linked sites to our website.

We only accumulate personally identifiable information that you select to share with us while registering. In order to provide you requested information/services or content, we may ask for personal information while registering. Further, we collect the email address of our valued clients who decide to communicate with us through mails for updates related to deals, offers, and discounts. Your other personal details such as gender, postal address, date of birth, feedback/suggestions, job role, occupation, views, survey information can be shared/provided by you on our discussion forums or other pages on our website.

You may notice that User Information (if shared) available on public domain such as forums is accessible for all users and visitors to the website. You are suggested to act cautiously before you share your personal details publicly, we do not support any claim or liability of misuse of information that you share with third party or such party unfamiliar to us. We warmly welcome you to join our discussion forums to share your ideas, deals and suggestions as well as to keep you informed about our latest deals, discounts, special price offers, services and products to make your shopping experience remarkable. Until you terminate your membership with us, all data transferred by you with us in the form of penned discussion, feedback given by you, email responses, forum discussions, contents posted on our website, known property rights personified within, shall be, for all reasons, be considered as our property and might be authorized wholly by us for specific use.

We do not obtain your information until you knowingly share with us. In order to provide you a user-oriented online shopping platform fully equipped with user generated contents, we utilize this information.

We do not sell, share, deal or trade in your personal information in any way apart from the manner already mentioned.

We also gather several other details from you when you visit our website, including your browser type, operating system, IP address, ISP (internet service provider), and the URL of previous website you visited. This information might not be consumed to individually recognize you. This non-personal information is being used for several purposes including managing the website; troubleshoot connection issues, to collect demographic information, to determine how our visitors use our website, to estimate visitors’ frequency, duration of visit, pages navigation, association and compliance with applicable law etc.

With the use of ‘cookies’ we automatically collect the non-personal information. Cookies are little text files that a website places on the hard drive of user’s computer to identify replicate users and assist user to use the website. These cookies helps us to follow the consumer behavior and collect total data to improve content, target advertising, promotional and marketing purposes.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our website. It should be noticed that we might not control the use of cookies by advertisers and third party websites. Some browsers allow users to disallow cookies, but users should note that cookies might be necessary to give several features of a website.

The users on our website have the opportunity to ‘opt-in’ to check their information consumed for the reasons not directly associated to us at the point when we ask for data. We do not give recognized data to other companies and instead, consume this data for its own purposes including but not limited to email newsletters, until the user ‘opt-in’ by selectively permitting consumption. After subscription, those users who do not want to get our notifications or newsletter may ‘opt-out’ (discontinue receiving) of such notification by answering to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or contact us. In every email we send, we give opt-out system in the text.

If personally identifiable data of users such as phone, email address, physical address, zip code etc changes or if a user does not want to obtain our services, we allow them a way to edit, change, delete, update or correct this information.

We try our best to secure user privacy; we might reveal personal information when legally required.

Sometime, we need to send urgent announcements when needed. For example, we send emails to our users in case of service suspension and website maintenance. Usually, users cannot opt-out of these notifications while they may deactivate their account. Nevertheless, these communications are not promotional in any way.

We make all possible efforts to preserve the personal information revealed to the site. Conversely, we are not liable for any type of breach of security. If any user identifiably share personal information including email, name, or any other type of data in a forum or other public services, then he must be familiar with the fact that this information can be used by third parties. Although, while registering, a user can select whether an email is to be disclosed in profile or post of forum user.

Users who subscribe to newsletters or email notifications with us will often receive mails possessing the updates about improvements and changes as well as offers of our website. This may also include exclusive promotions, products and service information or special deals. This type of communications will solely come from us (as we shall never sell your email addresses) and there shall always be the choice to ‘opt-out’ of such particular broadcast emails.

Children under 18 should not be allowed to put any type of information unless allowed by parents or guardians. We do not manage the users’ or audiences age.

We own the rights to alter this policy anytime by posting notice of the presence of a new privacy statement. If we make decision of changing our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage and other places we believe it to be appropriate so our users stay updated about the information we collect, how we utilize it and under what situations, if any, we reveal it. We shall utilize data in association with the privacy policy under which the information was gathered.

**  Disclaimer**

We do not claim to be liable or favoring the information, products or services these sites offer. We are not associated or have any union with any site linked to us in any way. All material on our website is given only for the purpose of general information.

The policies and the statement summarized here are not proposed to and do not make any legal or contractual rights in or to represent any party.
